{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Interacting with people makes me feel good. ?",
      "choices": ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "My goals in life are clear ?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "If people are rude to me I just shrug it off ?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Disagree"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am confident in what I do ?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "I can work even when things are disorganized ?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Disagree"
    },
    {
      "question": "I consistently put full time and effort into everything I do?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "I prefer achieving my goals than assisting others to achieve their goals?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Disagree"
    },
    {
      "question": "I would describe myself as an extremely competent person?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Disagree"
    },
    {
      "question": "I prefer working within a stable rather than flexible environment ?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Disagree"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am ambitious ?",
      "choices":  ["Agree", "Disagree"],
      "answer": "Agree"
    }
    
  ]
}